Guide to the Western Pennsylvania Conservancy Records and Photographs, 1885-2006 AIS.1999.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1885-2006; 1950-2004; II.
  - Community Garden Program, 1975-2006; 1988-2004; 2.
    - 51. Vaughn's Seeds, Kissimmee, IL., 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - A. Anderson Street Bridge, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - B. Birmingham Bridge, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - C. East Liberty, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - D. Highland Park Bridge, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - E. Highland Park, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - F. McKees Rocks, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - G. McKees Rocks Bridge, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - H. Northside Site, Before Starburst Sculpture, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - I. Point State Park, Before, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - J. Point State Park, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - K. Point State Park, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - L. Point State Park, Fountain, Ground and from State Office Building, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 71)
    - M. Soldiers and Sailors, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - N. Soldiers and Sailors, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 73)
    - O. Soldiers and Sailors, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 74)
    - P. Soldiers and Sailors, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 75)
    - Q. Spring Garden, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - R. Northside Police Station; Hill District Police Station; Point State Park; West Park Circle; Northside; and Troy Hill Parklet, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 77)
    - S. Soldiers and Sailors; Bloomfield; and Allegheny Cemetery, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 78)
    - T. Variety Pack, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 79)
    - U. Variety Pack, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 80)
    - V. Variety Pack, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 81)
    - W. Brighton Road and Western Avenue, 1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 82)
    - X. Troy Hill Fence, 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 83)
    - A. Birmingham Bridge, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 84)
    - B. East Liberty; and Lawrenceville Gardens, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 85)
    - C. Highland Park, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 86)
    - E. Highland Park, July 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 87)
    - F. Hill District Police Station; Liberty Tunnel; and Northside Police Station, 1990; Prints (Box 53, Folder 88)
    - G. Liberty Tunnel Construction, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 89)
    - H. Liberty Tunnel Construction, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 90)
    - I. Liberty Tunnel, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 91)
    - J. McKees Rocks, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 92)
    - K. McKees Rocks Bridge, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 93)
    - L. North Avenue and Brighton Road; and West Northside, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 94)
    - M. Point State Park, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 95)
    - N. Stephen Foster; and Spring Garden, 1990; Prints (Box 53, Folder 96)
    - O. Troy Hill, 1990; Prints (Box 53, Folder 97)
    - P. Troy Hill, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 98)
    - Q. West End, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 99)
    - R. West Park Circle, 1990; Prints (Box 53, Folder 100)
    - S. Northside Sculpture Starburst, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 101)
    - T. Liberty Tunnel; Birmingham Bridge; and Market Square, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 102)
    - U. Liberty Tunnel; East Liberty; Stadium; West End, Wabash Street; Hill District Church; McKinley Park; 42nd Street; and Ravilla Street, 1990; Prints (Box 53, Folder 103)
    - V. Liberty Tunnel; Birmingham Bridge; and McKees Rocks Bridge, May 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 104)
    - W. Highland Park Bridge; Stadium; Parkway; and Fort Pitt Tunnel Area, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 105)
    - X. Northside Sculpture; McKees Rocks Bridge; Spring Garden; West Park Circle; Three Rivers Youth; and North Avenue and Brighton Road, July 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 106)
    - Y. West End, Wabash Street; and Meadow Street Community Garden, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 107)
    - Z. Spring Garden; Stephen Foster; West Park Circle; Northside Sculpture; and Troy Hill, July 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 108)
    - AA. Birmingham Bridge; Liberty Tunnel; Market Square; Point State Park; and Stephen Foster, July 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 109)
    - BB. Three Rivers Youth; East Liberty; Liberty Tunnel; and Meadow Street, February 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 110)
    - CC. Three Rivers Youth; Market Square; Point State Park; and Stephen Foster, July 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 111)
    - DD. Three Rivers Youth; Highland Park Bridge; East Liberty; Lawrenceville Gardens; Point Breeze; and Meadow Street Community Garden, July 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 112)
    - EE. Three Rivers Youth; Highland Park Bridge; Liberty Bridge; and Carrick High Rise, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 113)
    - FF. Three Rivers Youth; 42nd Street Community Garden; and Lawn Street, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 114)
    - GG. East Liberty; Highland Park Bridge; Point Breeze; Three Rivers Youth; 42nd Street Community Garden; and Meadow Street Community Garden, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 115)
    - HH. Liberty Tunnel; West End; and Troy Hill, July 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 116)
    - II. Garden Tour, 1990; Prints (Box 53, Folder 117)
    - JJ. Light of Life Mission, 1990; Prints (Box 53, Folder 118)
    - A. East Park; and Venture Street, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 119)
    - B. Brighton Road; South Dallas Avenue; and Chestnut Street, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 120)
    - C. Grant Street; Greenfield; Chestnut Street; Venture Street; and Formosa Street, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 121)
    - E. Greenfield; Chestnut Street; Allegheny Cemetery; and Etna, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 122)
    - F. Grant Street; Chestnut Street; South Dallas Avenue; and Nash Street Parklet, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 123)
    - G. East Park; and South Dallas Avenue, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 124)
    - H. Venture Street; North Avenue and Brighton Street; and Chestnut Street, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 125)
    - I. East Park; Chestnut Street; and Northside Sculpture, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 126)
    - J. East Park; Brighton Road; and Mexican War Street Parklet, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 127)
    - K. Grant Street; McKees Rocks; Venture Street; and Charles Street and Brighton Road, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 128)
    - L. North Avenue and Brighton Road; East Park; West Park Circle; and Spring Garden, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 129)
    - M. Grant Street; and South Dallas Avenue, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 130)
    - N. Chestnut Street; Spring Garden; Troy Hill Parklet; Troy Hill Community Garden; and Elbow Street, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 131)
    - O. East Park; West Park Circle; North Avenue and Brighton Road; Troy Hill; and Charles Street and Brighton Road, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 132)
    - P. Chestnut Street; and Troy Hill, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 133)
    - Q. Birmingham Bridge; Stephen Foster; and Greenfield, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 134)
    - R. Chestnut Street; and Southside Riverfront, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 135)
    - S. South Dallas Avenue, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 136)
    - T. Birmingham Bridge; Stephen Foster; McKees Rocks Bridge; Grant Street; Greenfield; and Venture Street, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 137)
    - U. Chicago Ball Seed Co., 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 138)
    - V. Super Playground; Point State Park; and Highland Park, 1991; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 139)
    - A. Riverview Park; and Success Street, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - B. Fifth Avenue; Manchester; Broadhead Manor; Burrows; and Polish Hill, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - C. Polish Hill; Manchester; and Western Avenue, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - D. North Avenue and Brighton Road; Manchester; and Mexican War Streets, Mechanics Park, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - E. Polish Hill; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; and Stephen Foster, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - F. Manchester; North Avenue and Brighton Road; Brighton Road and Charles Street; West Park Circle; and East Park, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - G. Highland Park, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - I. McKees Rocks; West End; Broadhead Manor; Steuben Street; and Liberty Tunnel, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - J. Chestnut Street; Riverview Park; Spring Garden; and Venture Street, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - K. McKees Rocks; and Riverview Park, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - L. South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; Stephen Foster; and West Park Circle, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - M. Point State Park, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - N. Highland Park; East Liberty; and Beechwood Boulevard and Reynolds Street, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - O. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds Judging, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - P. Chicago Ball Seed Co.; Catigny Park, IL.; Toledo, OH.; and Polish Hill, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Q. Columbus, Ohio, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - R. Columbus, Ohio, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - S. Denver, Colorado, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - T. Foreign Gardens, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - U. Homewood Brushton Community Improvement Association, Inc.; and Kelly Street and Braddock Avenue, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - V. Perrysville Avenue and Federal Street, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - W. Linden Avenue and McPherson Boulevard, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - X. Mexican War Street Community Garden, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Y. Duplicates: Birmingham Bridge; Grant Street; Stephen Foster; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; and East Park, 1992; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - A. Bloomfield; Hill District Police Station; Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; and Polish Hill, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - B. Stephen Foster; Anderson Street Bridge; and Greenfield, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - C. Golf Course; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; Beechwood Boulevard and Reynolds Street; and Linden Circle, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - D. Steuben Street; Mount Washington; Manchester; McKees Rocks; West End; Riverview Park; East Park; and Spring Garden, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - E. Bloomfield; Grant Street; Van Braam; Brighton Road and North Avenue; Brighton Road and Charles Street; Taylor Street Parklet; Northside Police Station; West Park Circle; and Chestnut Street, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - F. Carson Street and Sarah Street; Birmingham Bridge; Liberty Tunnel; Mount Washington; Grant Street; Spring Garden; West End; West Park Circle; and Chestnut Street, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - G. Homewood, Bennett Community Garden; Frankstown; and Highland Park, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - H. Van Braam; Homewood, Bennet Street Community Garden; and Bloomfield, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - I. Point State Park; and Grant Street, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - J. Greenfield, Upper; Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; and Southside, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - K. Mount Washington, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - L. Southside; Fransktown Avenue and Bennett Street; and Greenfield, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - M. Chestnut Street and East Ohio Street; Mount Washington; Southside; and Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - N. Mount Washington, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - O. Bloomfield; Buena Vista Street; Carson Street and Sarah Street; Collier Township; Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; Formosa Street; Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; Greenfield; Lincoln Avenue and Larimer Avenue; Mount Washington; Panther Hollow Lake; and Sherman Street and Mexican War Street Community Garden, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - P. Panther Hollow Lake, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Q. Norman Street, Northside, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - R. Carson Street and Sarah Street; Birmingham Bridge; Liberty Tunnel; and Mount Washington, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - S. East Liberty, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - T. Fifth Avenue; Van Braam; Chicago; Milwaukee; and Castor Bean Plant, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - U. East Liberty; and Bass Tournament, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 45)
    - V. Garden Luncheon, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 46)
    - W. Garden Luncheon, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 47)
    - X. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 48)
    - Y. Longwood Gardens, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 49)
    - Z. Schenley Park Plaza, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 50)
    - AA. Tree Sculpture, Maria Nordman, 1993; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 51)
    - BB. Beaver, 1994; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 52)
    - OO. Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund Garden Tour, 1995; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 53)
    - PP. Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund Garden Luncheon, Portland, Oregon, 1995; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 54)
    - QQ. Liberty Tunnel Sign; and Polish Hill Sign, 1995; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 55)
    - ZZ. Duplicates: California Avenue and Termon Avenue; and Allegheny River Boulevard and Washington Boulevard, 1995; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 56)
    - ZZ1. Duplicate Picture Boards: Carson Street; Manchester; Highland Park; Mifflin School; Liberty Tunnel; West Park Circle; and California Avenue and Termon Avenue, 1995; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 57)
    - ZZ2. Duplicate Picture Boards: California Avenue and Termon Avenue; Lincoln Elementary School; and Mifflin School, 1995; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 58)
    - ZZ3. Duplicate Picture Boards: Allegheny River Boulevard; Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; Highland Park; Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue; and Mount Washington, 1995; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 59)
    - A. Carnegie; Collier Township; Duquesne; Emsworth; Ohio Township; South Fayette Township, Bridgeville; and Thornburg, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 60)
    - B. Kennedy Township; Rankin Bridge; Mckeesport; and North Versailles, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 61)
    - C. Noblestown Road and Durbin Street; Charles Street and Knox Avenue; Penn Avenue and Braddock Avenue; McKees Rocks Bridge; and Centre Avenue and South Aiken Avenue, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 62)
    - D. Bethel Park; Castle Shannon Boulevard; Church Hill; East Pittsburgh: Route 30 and Westinghouse Bridge, Tri-Boro Expressway and Electric Avenue; Forest Hills, Ardmore Boulevard; Mt. Lebanon, Washington Boulevard; Penn Hills, Coal Hollow and Frankstown Avenue; Ross Township, Rochester and Perrysville; Shaler, Route 8; Tarentum; Wilkinsburg: and Ardmore and Parkway, Laketon and Robinson, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 63)
    - E. Edgewood, Braddock Avenue and Parkway; Hampton, Route 8 and East Hardies; Harmarville, Route 910 and Freeport Road; Heidlersburg, Route 50 and Greentree Road; Homestead: 8th Avenue, High Level Bridge; McKeesport: O'Neil Boulevard and Eden Park Boulevard, Walnut Street and Route 48, 15th Street Bridge; Natrona Heights, Freeport Road; Port Vue; Ross Township, McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; West Mifflin: Route 885 and Old Elizabeth Road, Municipal Building; White Oak, Lincoln and Route 48; and Truck Bed Accident, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 64)
    - F. Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard and Saline Street; Allegheny River Boulevard and Washington Boulevard; McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Braddock Avenue and Penn Avenue; and Jitney Garden in Homewood, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 65)
    - G. Kirwin Heights; Route 885 and Century III Mall; West and 15th Street; McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Route 8 and Butler Plank; Route 8 and East Hardies; Route 910 and Freeport; Freeport, Millis, and Ross; Braddock Avenue and Parkway; Rankin Bridge; Dormont Pool; Mansfield Avenue and Campbells Run Road; Electric Avenue and Tri-Boro Expressway; Route 48 and Walnut Street; O'Neil Boulevard and Eden Park Boulevard; Walnut Street and Fifth Avenue; and Noblestown Road and Durbin Street, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 66)
    - H. Rankin Bridge; Allegheny River Boulevard and Washington Boulevard; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; Jitney Garden in Homewood; Shady Lane School at Braddock Avenue and Penn Avenue; and Dormont Pool, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 67)
    - I. McKnight Road and McIntyre Road; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; North Braddock Avenue; Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard, and Saline Street; and Rankin Bridge, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 68)
    - J. Mansfield Avenue and Campbells Run Road; McKnight Road and McIntyre Road; Noblestown Road and Durbin Street; and Dormont Avenue, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 69)
    - K. Schenley Park Plaza; Chuck Robertson; Tools and Equipment; and Birmingham Bridge, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 70)
    - L. Riverview Park; Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; and Point State Park, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 71)
    - M. California Avenue and Termon Avenue; and McKees Rocks Bridge, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 72)
    - N. Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue Community Garden, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 73)
    - O. Rankin Bridge; Noblestown Road and Durbin Street; North Braddock Avenue and Penn Avenue; McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Dormont Avenue; Mansfield Avenue and Campbells Run Road; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; Jitney Station; and Alma Illery Health Center, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 74)
    - P. Rankin Bridge; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; Linden Avenue; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; Morrowfield Avenue, Tilbury Street, and Beechwood Boulevard; and Hazelwood Avenue, Saline Street, and Beechwood Boulevard, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 75)
    - Q. McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; North Braddock Avenue and Penn Avenue; Morrowfield Avenue, Tilbury Street, and Beechwood Boulevard; and Hazelwood Avenue, Saline Street, and Beechwood Boulevard, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 76)
    - R. Rankin Bridge, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 77)
    - S. Dormont Avenue; Mansfield Avenue and Campbells Run Road; Noblestown Road and Durbin Street; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; and McIntyre Road and McKnight Road, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 78)
    - T. Rankin Bridge; Northgate High School; North Avenue and Brighton Road; Manchester; Steuben Street Water Break; Davis Parklet, Hobart Street; Richmond Street and Sanders Street; South Saint Clair Street; Marshall Road and Norwood, Riverview Park; Lookout Street, Troy Hill; Balf Park, Bellevue; Philips Elementary School; and Alma Illery Arts Feastable Garden, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 79)
    - U. Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; Crawford Street and Centre Avenue; Fifth Avenue; Mount Washington; and Mifflin School, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 80)
    - V. Mifflin School; Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue; Beechwood Boulevard and Reynolds Street; and Rankin Bridge, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 81)
    - W. Birmingham Bridge; Carson Street and Sarah Street; Dormont Avenue; Mansfield Boulevard and Campbells Run Road; Steuben Street and Middletown Road; West End; Philips Elementary School; and 10th Ward, McKeesport, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 82)
    - X. Birmingham Bridge; Carson Street and Sarah Street; California Avenue and Termon Avenue; Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard and Saline Street; McKees Rocks; and Mount Washington, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 83)
    - Y. Chestnut Street; East Park; West Park Circle; Northside Police Station; Spring Garden; Riverview Park; Venture Street; and The Mattress Factory, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 84)
    - Z. California Avenue and Termon Avenue; McKees Rocks Bridge; Penn Avenue and Friendship Avenue; and Riverview Park, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 85)
    - AA. Point State Park, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 86)
    - AA1. Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; and Homewood Area, Mrs. Savage, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 87)
    - BB. West Park Circle; East Park; North Shore Park; Polish Hill; Greenfield, Upper; and Greenfield, Lower, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 88)
    - CC. Grant Street; McKees Rocks Bridge; Mount Washington; Carson Street and Sarah Street; Hill District Police Station; and Polish Hill, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 89)
    - DD. Brighton Road and Charles Street; Manchester; North Avenue and Brighton Road; Allegheny River Boulevard and Washington Boulevard; and Highland Park, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 90)
    - EE. Highland Park; East Liberty; Schenley Park Plaza; Stephen Foster; Anderson Street Bridge; and Greenfield, Lower, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 91)
    - FF. Garden Tour, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 92)
    - GG. Point State Park; Chicago Ball Seed Co.; Cantigny Park; and Milwaukee, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 54, Folder 93)
    - HH. Small Grants: Duquesne, McKeesport, and Mon-Yough Community Services, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - II. Nashville, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - JJ. Garden Tour, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - KK. Small Grants, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - LL. Quebec City, Canada, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - MM. Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund Garden Luncheon, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - NN. Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund Garden Luncheon, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - OO. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 8)